{
  "German": {
    "Lesson1": [
      { "question": "het broodje", "answer": "das Brötchen" },
      { "question": "de kaas", "answer": "der Käse" },
      { "question": "de ham", "answer": "der Schinken" },
      { "question": "de tonijn", "answer": "der Thunfisch" },
      { "question": "de ui", "answer": "die Zwiebel" },
      { "question": "de tafel", "answer": "der Tisch" },
      { "question": "krijgen", "answer": "bekommen" },
      { "question": "het drankje", "answer": "das Getränk" }
    ],
    "Lesson2": [
      { "question": "de rekening", "answer": "die Rechnung" },
      { "question": "de vorken", "answer": "die Gabeln" },
      { "question": "de suiker", "answer": "der Zucker" },
      { "question": "de borden", "answer": "die Teller" },
      { "question": "het toetje", "answer": "der Nachtisch" },
      { "question": "de lepel", "answer": "der Löffel" },
      { "question": "genomen", "answer": "genommen" },
      { "question": "heet", "answer": "heiß" },
      { "question": "Eet smakelijk", "answer": "Guten Appetit" }
    ],
    "Lesson3": [
      { "question": "het vlees", "answer": "das Fleisch" },
      { "question": "de schnitzels", "answer": "die Schnitzel" },
      { "question": "het restaurant", "answer": "das Restaurant" },
      { "question": "de glazen", "answer": "die Gläser" },
      { "question": "de soepen", "answer": "die Suppen" },
      { "question": "de kopjes", "answer": "die Tassen" },
      { "question": "de restaurants", "answer": "die Restaurants" },
      { "question": "de lepels", "answer": "die Löffel" },
      { "question": "de patat, friet", "answer": "die Pommes" },
      { "question": "het ingrediënt", "answer": "die Zutat" }
    ]  
  },
  "French": {
    "Lesson1": [
      { "question": "Translate to German: \"apple\"", "answer": "Apfel" }
    ]
  }
}

